studyinternational.com 2019-12-23

# Privacy Policy | Study International

**Privacy Policy of[http://www.studyinternational.com](http://www.studyinternational.com/)**

This website (hereinafter “Website”) collects some Personal Data from its Users. The Data are collected and processed for the purposes set out below.

**Data Processing Ownership**

Study International part of Hybrid News Limited - Colston Tower, Level 9, Colston St, Bristol. UNITED KINGDOM. BS1 4UX

**Types of Data collected**

Among the Data that this Website may collect there are: Cookie, Browsing and usage Data, First Name, Last Name, Date of Birth, Phone number, Address, State, Email and ZIP/Postal code. Other Personal Data collected may be highlighted by other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text, in the moment when the Data collection happens. The Personal Data may be freely inserted by the User or the Data Subject, or collected automatically when using the Website. Any use of Cookies by the Website or the owners of third party services used by the Website, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify the User and remember his/her preferences for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User. Failure to provide certain Personal Data, in particular Navigation Data, by deactivating the Website’s Cookies may make it impossible to surf or for the Website to provide its services. The Personal Data collected may regard both the User and third parties whose data the User provides. The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through the Website and declares that (s)he has the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Owner of all responsibility towards third parties. Mode and place of processing the Data obtained

**Method of Processing**

The Data Controller processes the Data of the Interested Parties and Users in a lawful and proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data. Processing is carried out using computers and / or telematic means, with organizational methods and logics strictly related to the stated purposes. In addition to the owner, in some cases, access to the Data may be available to external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies). The updated list of Managers may be requested from the Owner at any time. Place The Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.

**Conservation Time**

The Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by the User, and the User can always ask for their suspension or removal. The use of the collected Data The Data concerning the User or the Data Subject are collected for the following purposes: Analytics and Contacting the User. The kinds of Personal Data used for each purpose are given in the specific sections of this document. The use of Data for additional purposes by the Owner may in some cases, and for legal purposes, require specific consent by the User or the Data Subject. Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data and the services provided by third parties Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services: The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behaviour.

**Google Analytics (Google)**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine Website use, to prepare reports on an Website’s activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected: Browsing and usage Data and Cookie. Place of Processing: USA – Privacy Policy.

**Contact form (This Website)**

By filling in the Contact form with their Data, the Users authorizes the Website to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header. Personal data collected: Address, Date of Birth, Email, First Name, Last Name, Phone number, State and ZIP/Postal code. Additional information about data processing

**Legal Protection**

The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner of the Website in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from its improper use or that of related services by the User.

**Additional Information**

Specific information may be shown on the pages of the Site concerning particular services or the processing of Data provided by the User or by the Data Subject.

**Maintenance**

The User’s Personal Data may be further used in ways and for purposes required for Website maintenance.

**System Logs**

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third party services it uses may collect system logs, i.e., files that record interaction – including navigation. They may also contain personal data, such as IP addresses.

**Information not contained in this policy**

More information on processing Personal Information may be requested from the Owner at any time.

**The Rights of Data Subjects**

Those persons to whom the Data refer have the right, at any time, to know whether their data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Owner of the Processing System.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

The Website reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page, and by ensuring analogous protection of the Personal Information in all cases. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. Information about this privacy policy.

**Personal information or Data**

Any information regarding a natural person, a legal person, an institution or an association, which is, or can be, identified, even indirectly, by reference to any other information, including a personal identification number.

**Browsing and usage Data**

Information collected automatically from the Site, including the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the users who connect to the site, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server's answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the visitor, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page) and the details about the path followed within the site with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the operating system and the user's IT environment. User Means the individual user of the Website’s services or products.

**Data Subject**

The legal or natural person to whom the Personal Data refer.

**Data Processor**

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other organization, association or organization designated by the Data Controller for the Personal Data processing system.

**Data Controller**

The natural person, legal person, public administration or any other body, association or organization with the right, also jointly with another Data Controller, to make decisions regarding the purposes, and the methods of processing of Personal Data and the means used, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this Site.

**Legal information**

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfilment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies. This privacy policy exclusively regards this Website.
